压制:随Feng
No Limit
没有极限
歌手：Befour
Let me hear ya say yeah! (yeah!)
让我听到你们大声说 YEAH
No,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no there's no limit!
没有...没有...没有极限
no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no there's no limit!
No no limits, we'll reach for the sky!
没有极限 我们可触及天际
No valley to deep
没有深不可达
No mountain too high
没有高不可攀
No no limits, won't give up the fight!
没有极限 永不放弃斗志
We do what we want and we do it with pride
我们为所欲为 我们骄傲自豪
Hard to the core, I feel the floor
狂摇热舞 与音乐融为一体
When I'm on stage, yo, ya answer more
我一上舞台 你们就反应热烈
I'm on the ass, I know the last, I work real hard to collect my cash!
我穷困潦倒 我不甘落后 为了赚钱我玩命工作
Tick tick ticka tick take your time, when I'm goin' I'm goin' for mine
时钟滴答作响 不要性急 我奋斗的时候 是在为了自已
Open your ears and you will hear it
竖起耳朵认真听好
I tell you this 'cause there's no limit!
我告诉你一切没有极限
No,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no there's no limit!
没有...没有...没有极限
no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no,no there's no limit!
No no limits, we'll reach for the sky!
没有极限 我们可触及天际
No valley to deep
没有深不可达
No mountain too high
没有高不可攀
No no limits, won't give up the fight!
没有极限 永不放弃斗志
We do what we want and we do it with pride
我们为所欲为 我们骄傲自豪
Hey yeah no no
没有...没有...
Oh hey yeah no no
No limits allowed, cause there's much crowd
尽情放纵 人潮汹涌
Microphone check as I choose my rhyme
选好节奏检查麦克风
I'm playing on the road, I've got no fear
当众表演 我豪无畏惧
The sound from my mouth is the rap you hear
嘴中的声音是我的说唱
No valley too deep, no mountain too high
没有深不可达 没有高不可攀
Reach the top, touch the sky!
到达顶峰 触及天际
They tried to diss me cause I sell out
因我卖得太好有人想攻击我
I'm making techno when I am proud!
得意之时我总作舞曲
No no limits, we'll reach for the sky!
没有极限 我们可触及天际
No valley to deep
没有深不可达
No mountain too high
没有高不可攀
No no limits, won't give up the fight!
没有极限 永不放弃斗志
We do what we want and we do it with pride
我们为所欲为 我们骄傲自豪
No no limits, we'll reach for the sky!
没有极限 我们可触及天际
No valley to deep
没有深不可达
No mountain too high
没有高不可攀
No no limits, won't give up the fight!
没有极限 永不放弃斗志
We do what we want and we do it with pride
我们为所欲为 我们骄傲自豪
压制:随Feng